Leena Prashanthi Kakarla

Phone no: 8374510026, Hyderabad, Email: prashanthileena@gmail.com Pin:500089.

Professional Summary:-

Reliable with 5.2 years of hands-on experience and dedicated work ethic. Self-motivated to consistently deliver top-notch results while meeting strict objectives and deadlines. Dedicated with experience in achieving tangible results and cross-team collaboration. Proactive and enthusiastic about working with peers to achieve goals.

Education:

Masters in Science[M.Sc] [2010-2012]

Siddhartha P.G College

Two years graduation course in Microbiology

Bachelors of science [B.Sc] [2007-2010]

Kavitha Memorial Degree College

Three years graduation course in Bio-Technology, Botany and Chemistry

Intermediate [2005-2007]

Saahithi Junior College

Two years under graduation course in Botany, Zoology, Physics and chemistry.

SSC [2004-2005]

Margadarshini English medium school.

Technical Skills:-

Windows XP, Windows 7 & Windows 8, MS Office Suite (Word, Excel, PowerPoint) **Health care Applications** – Pharmacy Accounts Receivable System, WebSDL, Mobius, Business Objects.

Professional Experience:

Worked as an Administrative Officer in Santhinikethan Concept School from Sept 2012 to March 2015.

Worked as a Process Developer for Walgreens process under HAR (Healthcare Accounts Receivables) at Genpact from March 2015 to Oct 2017.

Roles and Responsibilities:

Organisation-Genpact (2015-2017)

Designation - Process Associate

- Worked for Walgreens under HAR (healthcare Accounts receivables)
- Performed PEX (Payment Exceptions) activities such as invalid payment refunds, patient refunds, revenue adjustments, mailing checks.
- Worked on non-federal insurance plans like Cigna, Aetna & Blue cross Blue shield.
- Processed all types of reimbursements received from insurance companies and resolved them in the best possible manner to obtain maximum reimbursement.
- Ensured mandatory fields are filled to process a claim.
- Processed Claims with zero critical errors and complete claims transaction volumes in queue within the specified TAT.
- Maintained consistent quality and ensure error free invoice and payment processing.

Designation - Process Developer

- Managed a team of 8 accounts receivable analysts.
- Handled the PEX process (payment exceptions).
- Processed critical receivables (Valeant receivables) and also worked on CPI.
- Reviewed claims (quality control) that were processed by PEX staff.
- Maintained the strictest confidentiality adhered to all HIPAA guidelines/regulations.
- Worked daily on MS access activities.
- Transferred knowledge to new employees to ensure a smooth transition.
- Shared process knowledge to prepare SOP's.
- Worked on special projects according to client requirements.
- Trained new hires.
- Handled and resolved issues related to referral orders (RA).
- Responded to customer inquiries in an efficient manner.
- Took full responsibility for assigned task and ensured delivery.
- Billing Experience: -
- Worked on creating invoices to receive payments.
- Worked to retrieve all open balances via query from SAP based application called Business Objects.
- Reviewed the open balances to report queries to create an invoice.

Organisation – Santhinikethan Concept School(2012-2015) Designation – Administrative officer

- Ensured to develop and run educational programmes.
- Counselled students when needed.
- Handled scheduling, record-keeping and reporting.
- Managed budgets, logistics and events or meetings.
- Hired, trained and advised staff.
- Resolved conflicts and other issues.

Primary School Teacher: (Grades: 1-5)

Subjects – EVS & English

- Created and maintained a welcoming, friendly, engaging and nurturing classroom environment where all students felt comfortable.
- Developed rigorous lesson plans and lectures, prepared students for quizzes and tests.
- Graded papers, lessons, quizzes, tests and other assignments, relaying information to parents and school board when necessary.

Accomplishments:

- As part of Genpact was an active team member, was recognized as a consistent academic performer, received customer appreciation and an award.
- Lean-certified in the Walgreens process at Genpact.
- Trained and certified in Essential Communication Skills (GTA).
- Was promoted to the next level (Process Associate Process Developer) within the specified time frame.

Strengths:

- Proactive & Adaptable.
- Hardworking & Time Management.
- Multitasking.
- Feasible to adapt to change.
- Team Player.
- Ability to perform under pressure.
- Problem- Solving Skills.

PERSONAL PROFILE:

Gender : Female

Languages Known : English, Telugu, Hindi

Nationality : Indian

Declaration:

I hereby declare that all that information mentioned above is true to my knowledge.

Place: Hyderabad Signature

Date: